Act natural.
Hoppers is a family, comedy, animation film directed by Daniel Chong.
Scientists have discovered how to "hop" human consciousness into lifelike robotic
animals, allowing people to communicate with animals as animals.
Animal lover Mabel seizes an opportunity to use the technology, uncovering mysteries
within the animal world that are beyond anything she could have imagined.
Mabel Tanaka / Mabel Beaver (voice), played by Piper Curda.
King George (voice), played by Bobby Moynihan.
Mayor Jerry Generazzo (voice), played by Jon Hamm.
Dr. Sam (voice), played by Kathy Najimy.
Titus (voice), played by Dave Franco.
Loaf (voice), played by Eduardo Franco.
Hoppers is an upcoming American animated science fiction action comedy film
produced by Pixar Animation Studios for Walt Disney Pictures.
Directed by Daniel Chong from a screenplay by Jesse Andrews, the film
stars the voices of Piper Curda, Bobby Moynihan and Jon Hamm.
It follows an animal lover named Mabel whose mind is transferred into a lifelike robotic beaver
in order to communicate with animals and save their habitat from destruction.
Chong began working on a new original film at Pixar in December 2020.
The film was first officially announced as Hoppers in August 2024, along
with Curda, Moynihan, and Hamm revealed as part of the cast.
Hoppers is scheduled to be released in theaters in
the United States on March 6, 2026.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.